And to bring a divided state together and avoid riots and protests,
the way we did that was I knew half of South Carolinians saw the Confederate flag as heritage and tradition.
The other half of South Carolinians saw it as slavery and hate.
My job wasn't to judge either side.
My job was to get them to see the best of themselves and go forward.
And South Carolinians showed what true strength and grace look like because we didn't have protests.
We had vigils.
We didn't have riots.
We had prayer.
And South Carolina led the way.
But that is the way we have to work on issues that try and divide us is don't go and pick who's right and who's wrong and who's good and who's bad.
That's what leaders are doing now.
And it's caused us to be completely in political disarray.
A leader doesn't decide who's right.
When you serve the people, you serve everybody.
And your job is to give them all the information you have and let them know where you want to go going forward.
This is a load of bullshit because what she's doing here is she is conflating identifying political and movements that are harmful to the people with like individual people.
It's not about saying a person is right or wrong.
It's about saying that the ideologies that they are supporting are wrong because they are harmful to the society and the community of people that they share space with.
So when you are saying, oh, well, some people saw the Confederate flag as racism and slavery and others saw it as heritage, the reality is that it did represent racism and slavery.
And people who consider that to be their heritage can celebrate that in their own space, in their own time.
But for the government to celebrate that by literally flying representation of it is you saying that this government supports that as an ideology.
I'm so just disgusted by the way they're playing in our faces every day these days because people like this have a real shot at running this goddamn country.
And she is saying very clearly to you that she is in support of people who think that racism and slavery is fine and that as the leader of this country, she will give them space to carry that forward because she doesn't see it as her position to stop them.
These politicians are the worst of us because they don't actually serve the people.
They just serve the people that will serve them.
And that is matter of factly whoever has the most money.
They will tell the line, they will play both sides, they will smile on everybody's faces, and they will be given the opportunity to then determine the laws of the land and how people get to live their lives.
And that is based on which people have the most money in their pockets.
It's a sad state of affairs, y'all.
It's a sad state of affairs.
How do we stop people like this from being in position to change this country irreversibly and the way that you live your life?
We'll be talking about it at the InAmandaWeTrust live screenings that are going down all over this nation.
Go to AmandaSeals.com to get your tickets.
First stop, Chicago, January 19th.